As far as the maternity hospital...
The impact on the maternity hospital...
As far as the maternity hospital
and the health clinic in Yamane
we have seen
better reception conditions
for patients,
better reception conditions,
an improvement in reception conditions
We have a waiting room, a large waiting room,
a small room with chairs pushed together.
We also have beds,
we have two beds per room.
All rooms are equipped with beds.
There's a corner for newborns
with a delivery table.
Also in the delivery room,
we have a portable lamp
and a baby scale on site.
Everything is financed by Waitrose
We are really satisfied
with our partner, Waitrose
and we thank you very much
for the gesture you have made.
It has made us very happy,
not only as a population, but also
for us, as we are
the people in charge of the health clinic,
we are very satisfied, and happy.
We are grateful to you.
Really,
we thank you.
If you can introduce yourself just one more time please?
Oumou Khairy Deye,
state midwife,
head of the maternity hospital
at the health clinic in Yamane
I take care of prenatal consultations,
family planning,
gynecological consultation.
I do that too.
Consultations at the birth clinic.
All of this is done at the maternity hospital.
As well as deliveries.
We do deliveries too.
Perfect. Thank you.
OK