There are
lead, what!
For breakfast.
At breakfast, I take fresh cow's milk.
Sound.
So we're going to ask you to introduce your name.
What you do in the village who you are
and is where are we currently in which site we are?
My name is Ousman Sow
I live in the village of Ngallan
So at the level of this village, I manage.
I do a bit of animation at the social level.
By the way, I'm also a member of
this pub
called the farm.
And there, we do breeding,
vocational training and many other things.
The processing of fruit and vegetable products.
And There you go.
And therefore the project that will be supported
by the SPL and the Waitrose Foundation.
What will it bring to the village level?
The Baker
from college,
which is to be installed here at the village level of the Apple station
which is also supported
by the and the Metro Foundation.
It's a project that is close to my heart
the entire population of the area.
So to do this, we have a negative history.
Because
the village is seven kilometers away.
It was necessary that each time the students, because the mother,
every morning, she had to come in the evening.
That was really a real headache.
And that's how we could enjoy
of the installation of ADSL next door to effectively
try to find partners who can support us for really
an evening and a school that will solve all these words that I just said.
And in your opinion, what impact will it have on the education of children?
I believe that
the impact will be
very positive because I know there has been before.
There have been many young people who have dropped out of school
because of that distance.
I believe that once
this college is installed.
That's it.
Take.
Same.
A good
education.
To the studies carried out.
Get out school because it was.
To one.
Welcome from the road.
Et aussi the time Warner and
go to
great.